I mean, it's wild. Abi is actually Bea?
The puppet master who's been
manipulating Caloy
is actually Abi?
What we don't know right now
is what her motive is.
Your relationship with Caloy?
- We don't have a relationship.
- [JORDAN] You don't?
What did I ever do to you?
[ENRICO] How did you end up
living together anyway?
Billy tried to run away with Oliver
many times.
They lived in all sorts of places.
On the street…
Under the bridge…
That's when I decided to adopt them.
[MAN] Boss Zandro sent me.
He wanted to remind you
that no one has ever outsmarted him,
especially when it comes to money.
I'm glad you're back.
We really took a hit while you were gone.
[CAMILLE] I knew it wasn't a mistake
to give you another chance.
[BEA] Thank you again.
I can't believe Pebblng still took Bea in!
We should sue that delulu poser!
I agree.
I think we should drag her down
on social media.
[CHARM] I don't know who's crazier.
The poser or the company
that still took the poser in.
Better yet, I'll just get
both of their asses!
They're getting into my… blood vessels!
Calm down, guys.
This is exactly what they want.
To provoke us.
What if
we redirect this passion
into something more
useful?
Like our pilot project
for Happily Ever After.
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
And our first couple,
Melissa and Theo.
A cute and happy couple, at first glance.
They were already engaged
when Melissa called through LoveLine.
I got to talk to her,
and she mentioned that
her dad does not approve of Theo.
[MARIO] Why bring us here?
There's an Italian restaurant
near my favorite place anyway.
Dad, I told you they serve
the best gambas here, right?
Come on, you'll love it!
Just go along with your daughter.
Let's give it a try.
[MARIO] Okay. Let's order then.
[MARIO] Uh, waiter!
[MAN] Good evening, everyone.
Whoa, okay.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Isn't this…?
Uh, Theo, sir.
I hope you still remember me.
So, you're a waiter here?
This is our best-selling gambas.
Cooked with lemon, butter, and garlic.
It's my special recipe, sir,
so I made sure it's cooked
to perfection just for you.
Ah, so you're a chef then?
I'm a cook, sir.
The reason Melissa brought you here
is because, um…
[MELISSA] Uh…
Dad, Mom,
we want to ask for your blessing.
Uh, I've already saved up enough funds.
Just a little more and I'll be
a business partner
here at the restaurant and--
- Honey!
- Dad!
[BILLY] Melissa's dad
believes that Theo
doesn't deserve his daughter.
Melissa is a critically acclaimed
children's book author and illustrator,
while Theo is a cook at a restaurant.
Melissa's dad thinks she deserves better.
But!
They're both fighters
when it comes to love.
In the end, love wins!
They will push through with the wedding
with or without the father's blessing.
They stood their ground.
Mm-hmm.
Now we have this.
Kindly check for your reference
to get to know the couple better.
Please get one and pass.
I'll pass.
I'm jealous.
What?
I mean, I love her style! It's so magical!
Maybe we can use this as inspiration
for their wedding, right?
Charm, great idea!
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
A fairytale wedding.
[TONI] If we want it to be magical,
I know a supplier of crystals
and gemstones!
Not only for the aesthetic appeal,
but also for good luck
and prosperity as well.
[VALERIE] I have a friend
who is a costume designer.
She can take care of all
the costumes that we need.
[CHARM] We can also collaborate
with our visual design production partners
from our previous marketing events.
And Ralph and I also know wedding souvenir
and wedding booth suppliers.
[BILLY] But most importantly, we need
to be able to immortalize this event.
This can't be just beautiful.
It has to be meaningful.
It should be a testament to how hard
our couple fought for each other.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
What's going on? Why are you
only putting that on now?
What time did you even start?
Huh? Ma'am, look, it's crooked!
All you have to do
is line them up straight.
Your job's simple, so do it.
There's even four of you doing the work!
Hello, sir?
Wow, you've never left your spot!
You've been there since forever!
Every time I check, you're always there.
Go over there and fix things!
Wait, why is this here?
The LED display is getting blocked.
Move it aside here!
Put it over here.
Move it a bit to the side.
What the--? Just when did you get started?
Why do I still have to do this?
Morrie, where's Syd Hermosa, huh?
He's the event stylist, yet he's not here.
He only sent his people.
What's up with that?
He's still not here?
Let me give him a call.
- I'll call him.
- Please do.
We're about to start.
It's driving me nuts.
What about the seating arrangement?
Have you revised it already?
Yes, I already told them to get to it.
You told them? But that's your job!
Why did you have them do it?
It's not that hard!
Hold on, calm down
with your bossing around.
We're equals here.
Hm?
I'm just nervous.
I want everything to be perfect.
Sure. Perfect.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MAN] Okay, look at the camera.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
[PHOTOGRAPHER] Another pose!
[WHISPERING] Marj, let's try
to give off a happy vibe.
- [WHISPERING] Yeah.
- Her eyes.
Okay.
Um, Melissa?
Can we try, like, a bigger smile?
A brighter smile!
Like it's the happiest day of your life.
Is that okay?
Can we try one more?
- [CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
- Okay, smile!
- Okay, happier!
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Um, Melissa?
Are you okay?
I want to thank you
for making my dream wedding come true.
But it won't be complete.
Not without my dad.
- Marj.
- Sir, let's head outside first.
- Okay.
- Sir, let's give them space.
- You know, I'm an only child.
- Mm-hmm.
And I'm a daddy's girl.
[CRYING SOFTLY]
And the only reason
I believe in fairytales
is because growing up,
my dad made everything possible.
Mm-hmm.
For me, his princess.
[INHALES SHARPLY] You know,
he gave me everything I wanted.
Except for the most important thing to me.
His presence at my wedding.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TONI] Chief!
- Yes?
- Are the shots good to go?
Yes, they're editing it now for SDE.
But, chief,
it's as clear as day that the bride
doesn't seem to be happy.
Hmm…
Let's just do our best
to make our bride happy.
Mm-hmm. Okay. Mm-hmm.
Hey, did you know?
I got these flowers on a promo!
- They're beautiful!
- Excuse me!
Chief, we haven't gone over
our estimated expenses yet.
Oh, very good!
- Someone's happy.
- Perfect!
- Thank you, Blaire!
- Thank you!
How are things over here?
Sir, I told you that angle
makes it unflattering for the bride, gosh!
I agree. Let's try to shoot it
at an angle from above.
- Can we do that?
- Yes, ma'am.
Okay. Chief, what do you think?
Think it'll work?
Yes, we can try that.
Actually, I want to retake
these last few shots too.
I'll leave it to you, sir.
- All right, ma'am.
- Okay.
That way, the set will be
included in the shot.
Correct.
- That good, sir? Thank you!
- Yes, ma'am.
- [VALERIE] Please include…
- [CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
It says, "Happily Ever After." [CHUCKLES]
I thought I finally had that.
More like,
happily never after!
You sure about that?
Each fairytale has its own plot twist.
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
Just make sure the live feed
to the projector is synced to the cues.
- Okay?
- Yep.
- Don't forget.
- Dude, how's it going?
Let me see. The program,
the lights, the music…
The feed is live.
We've already rehearsed the cues.
Everything's good.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Okay, thank you.
- Chief, this is so beautiful!
- Mmm!
This is hand-painted?
The artist did amazing, huh?
Yeah! I wonder who the painter is?
[TONI] It's so cute!
Oh, there he is!
[JORDAN CLEARS THROAT]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
What are you doing here?
Joining you here
in your world.
What?
[YANI] Love…
I'm sorry.
I realized too late that
when you love someone,
you must also love
the things they hold dear.
Instead of being jealous over it,
I should be supporting you.
Rooting for you.
I should be your number one supporter.
Not just your Prince Charming.
I should be your sidekick. In everything.
[SMOOCHES] Love, I'm sorry.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[JORDAN LAUGHS]
So, are we ready,
Team LoveList?
For the love?
[IN UNISON] For the love, for the win!
[ALL CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
["WEDDING MARCH" PLAYING]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
Love the gown!
Care of Pebblng, of course.
Bea, I really love
the last-minute revisions.
So minimalist. So modern.
It's giving Korean wedding vibes.
This was their dream wedding, after all,
so we made it happen for them.
All right, we have 10,000 viewers
and counting!
A lot of people are reacting
on Pebblng's live broadcast!
- [CAMILLE] Perfect.
- There.
[MORRIE] "I love the theme!
It's very giving!"
- [PHONE CHIMES]
- "I want a Pebblng wedding."
"Congrats to LoveFeast!"
Yay! [APPLAUDING]
"Manifesting this with my match!"
Here's another one.
"Lord, please, 2026 Pebblng bride!"
I like that. I hope we get more of them.
- Oh, definitely.
- Hopefully, the views go up.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CHIMING]
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Theo.
May your happily ever after
begin with my blessing.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [MOUTHS] Wow.
[CELEBRANT] Dear friends and family,
we are gathered here today
to celebrate the union
of Theo and Melissa.
And to witness
the beginning of their journey
together in love and joy.
[MELISSA] My Theo,
I promise to be your home, your heart,
and your endless adventure,
now and for all the days to come.
[THEO] Melissa,
I vow to walk beside you
through every dream and every storm
as your love lights the path before us.
[CELEBRANT] By the power vested in me,
and in the presence
of your family and friends,
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
Theo, you may kiss your bride.
[CLAPPING, CHEERING]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[GREG] The good and the bad…
Why are they on their phones?
They're ruining the coverage.
[GREG] You were there for me.
Uh… Excuse me.
What are you watching?
The Happily Ever After event.
Okay, thank you.
They're watching Happily Ever After.
What the hell is Happily Ever After?
LoveList's event.
At the same time as ours?
I swear, Billy is doing this on purpose!
Their live stream has 500,000 views.
How many do we have?
Answer me!
Twelve thousand, Ms. Camille.
Only 12,000 views.
[CAMILLE] God!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
You may now kiss the bride.
[GUESTS CLAPPING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Which one of us is the bigger thief?
What's your reason for going after me?
I knew I needed your help, Ms. Billy.
Snake!
Of the two of us,
who's the fraud and the liar?
You! Jealous bastard!
[BILLY] Here, we're a family.
And in this family,
no one gets left behind.
[DOCTOR] Mr. Toledo is
cleared for discharge.
He may now be transferred
into your custody.
We have so much to celebrate.
- [BILLY, THEN EVERYONE] Cheers!
- [JORDAN] Cheers to that!
Hearts Island will be
our next biggest project.
Can we really pull it off?
Let's make a bet.
I can't win against you.
It's Jordan's birthday tomorrow.
Your and Billy's birthdays are
only a day apart, right?
- It's a double celebration!
- Yeah! Let's go!
Isn't it your birthday too?
It's tomorrow, Grandpa.
What's your wish,
my dear grandson?
Happiness for
the people
I care about the most.
[BEA] I don't think it would hurt
to give her a proper scare.